<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Adam Roegiest</title>
    <link>https://roegiest.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Adam Roegiest</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 04 Jan 2019 22:31:38 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://roegiest.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Publications</title>
      <link>https://roegiest.com/publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Jan 2019 22:31:38 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://roegiest.com/publications/</guid>
      <description>2019 Jonathan Donnelly, Adam Roegiest. On Interpretability and Feature Representations: An Analysis of the Sentiiment Neuron. ECIR 2019.
Winter Wei, Adam Roegiest. Mary Mikhail. From Bubbles to Lists: Designing Clustering for Due Diligence. CHIIR 2019.
Adam Roegiest, Anne McNulty. Variations in Assessor Agreement in Due Diligence. CHIIR 2019.
2018 Adam Roegiest, Winter Wei. Redesigning a Document Viewer for Legal Documents. CHIIR 2018.
Adam Roegiest, Alexander K. Hudek, Anne McNulty. A Dataset and an Examination of Identifying Passages for Due Diligence.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://roegiest.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Jan 2019 21:31:34 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://roegiest.com/about/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m a Research Scientist at Kira Systems based out of Toronto, Canada. Prior to Kira, I completed my PhD at the University of Waterloo under the supervision of Gordon V. Cormack (and sometimes Charlie Clarke, when Gordon was on sabbatical).
My primary interests are in the design and evaluation of human-in-the-loop (i.e., explicit feedback) Information Retrieval systems. This has generally been expressed through research in electronic discovery in civil litgation and due diligence law.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>